<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>index on James Diu&#39;s Blog</title>
		<link>/tags/index/</link>
		<description>Recent content in index on James Diu&#39;s Blog</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		
  		<language>en</language>
		
		<managingEditor>Page(/tags/index) (hugo author)</managingEditor>
    	
		<atom:link href="/tags/index/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>How to select a satisfying board game? Part 2</title>
			<link>/post/how-to-select-a-satisfying-board-game-part-2/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/how-to-select-a-satisfying-board-game-part-2/</guid>
			<description>Title Contents Testing Testing</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Test Rmarkdown</title>
			<link>/post/test-rmarkdown/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/test-rmarkdown/</guid>
			<description>Title Contents Test Rmarkdown</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Test Rmd</title>
			<link>/post/test-rmd/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/test-rmd/</guid>
			<description> no  Title Contents test Rmd
  </description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>How to select a satisfying board game? - Part I</title>
			<link>/post/how-to-select-a-satisfying-board-game/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/how-to-select-a-satisfying-board-game/</guid>
			<description>Being a boardgame enthusiasts, I always introduce board games to my friends. Some of them might be another enthusiasts, while some might have an idea that board game is equivalent to chess. Most of time I use my instinct and my understanding on the taste of my friends to decide which game would be provide the greatest fun for us. However, it can be very biased due to my personal preference.</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Course Wrap Up: Introduction to Data Science in Python</title>
			<link>/post/course-wrap-up-introduction-to-data-science-in-python/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/course-wrap-up-introduction-to-data-science-in-python/</guid>
			<description>After finishing my first python course in Coursera, it&amp;rsquo;s time to do a little summary.</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Topics</title>
			<link>/post/topics/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/topics/</guid>
			<description>P-hacking / Dredging
 Remedies:    Bonfereoni correction: reduce p-value when the number of t-test increases
  Hold-out sets: cross fold validation
  Investigation pre-registration: peer evaluation by professionals
  K-means
  Regression
  F test -&amp;gt; ANOVA
  AIC (Akaike Infomration criterion)
  Decision tree
  Contents </description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Case Study: The Ethics of Using Hacked Data: Patreon’s Data Hack and Academic Data Standards</title>
			<link>/post/case-study-the-ethics-of-using-hacked-data-patreon-s-data-hack-and-academic-data-standards/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/case-study-the-ethics-of-using-hacked-data-patreon-s-data-hack-and-academic-data-standards/</guid>
			<description>During the course I have read an interesting article about whether we should use the hacked data. ( Here is the article The Ethics of Using Hacked Data. ) In short, the case is about a reserach team found the data they failed to obtain from the provider, along with some other private or personal data, was hacked and released to public. Then there was a dicussion between whether it is appropiate to use the hacked data.</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Short Cut for Jyputer notebook</title>
			<link>/post/short-cut-for-jyputer-notebook/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/short-cut-for-jyputer-notebook/</guid>
			<description>Recently I am taking a online course in Coursra about data analysis with Python and therefore I started to use Jyputer notebook. In order to separate the text and code, a new crunk is required in Jyputer notebook, like Alt+Ctrl+i in Rmarkdown. Here are some short keys which I found useful.
   Short keys Function     Shift + Enter run the current cell, select below   Ctrl + Enter run selected cells   Alt + Enter run the current cell, insert below   Ctrl + S save and checkpoint    In command mode (press Esc to activate):</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>My first post with Blogdown (Small tips included!)</title>
			<link>/post/my-first-post-with-blogdown/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/my-first-post-with-blogdown/</guid>
			<description>Finally, I am starting my blog with blogdown! It takes a long time to establish it than I expected. Some Youtubes are now teaching how to build it within 15 min, which I have used much more than that! However, that is normal for someone like me without much experience with those Hugo, Netlify, and markdowns. To summerise all the steps I took, I would recommend reading the post from Martin Frigaard.</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
			<link>/post/markdown-syntax/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>/post/markdown-syntax/</guid>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
      	
	</channel>
</rss>
